<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Customer on</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/customers/</link><description>Recent content in Customer on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/customers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Affinity</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/customers/affinity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/customers/affinity/</guid><description>Get Affinity Partnership Retrieve information about the current Affinity Partnership. It will return available products and current status with insurers.
GET /v1/affinity/partnership
Response The above request returns JSON structured like this:
Parameter Description customer The complete customer data products List of products available for this affinity partnership products.id The ID of the current product products.name The name of the current product products.assists List of assists available for the product products.coverages List of coverages available for the product { &amp;#34;customer&amp;#34;: {}, &amp;#34;products&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;id&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;string&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;assists&amp;#34;: [], &amp;#34;coverages&amp;#34;: [] } ] } Create Affinity Request Before trying to create an affinity, you must create a affinity_request to &amp;ldquo;prepare&amp;rdquo; the process of contracting, receiving useful data for the rest of the process and to help proponent select desired configurations.</description></item><item><title>Recommendation</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/customers/recommendation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/customers/recommendation/</guid><description>The recommendation service uses Machine Learning models in order to predict the probability of a person to buy certain insurance products. It&amp;rsquo;s important that at the end of each recommendation, you evaluate the results in order to help training the models and improving his predictions.
Product Recommendation POST /v1/recommendations/product-type
Body Parameters The request has the following parameters in body:
Parameter Description input The recommendation value input Required input.product_type The product type Required input.</description></item></channel></rss>