<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/introduction/</guid><description>Our APIs itself was developed to cover the aspects of the digital distribution of insurance products. From now on, you are going to be presented with some of our integrations and services. You will be introduced to some of the core concepts of the insurance market, and how it works in a highly distributed and technological scope.
With any questions, please feel free to ask in our Developer Support channel, and may contribute to our FAQ.</description></item><item><title>About the Platform</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/about/</guid><description>The platform brings new technological visions, where it focuses on the optimization of processes and reduction of manual work following the latest and safest trends in the market. In the Project, we aim at adhering to processes linked to the legacy system platform with external channels for handling and digital insurance management, maintaining good market practices, technologies used for mass control, and providing multiple relationship channels for partners and direct customers.</description></item><item><title>REST APIs</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/rest/</guid><description>Representational state transfer (REST) is a software architectural style which uses a subset of HTTP. It is commonly used to create interactive applications that use Web services. A Web service that follows these guidelines is called RESTful.
Such a Web service must provide its Web resources in a textual representation and allow them to be read and modified with a stateless protocol and a predefined set of operations. Learn more</description></item><item><title>Client SDKs</title><link>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/client-sdks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://developers.onli.com.br/docs/introduction/client-sdks/</guid><description>Check for our SDKs See in our GitHub the client SDKs available to use in your favorite language.</description></item></channel></rss>